tonsofbuzz.com 2018-10-13

# Privacy Policy | Tons of Buzz

Your privacy is important to us.  
This Privacy and Information Security Policy (“the Policy”) discusses the personally identifiable information that we collect about you when you use our website and the other services we provide on or through the Site (together with the Site, the “Service”).

Policy highlights:

  * We will not collect personally identifiable information about you, including medical information, through the Service unless you disclose or authorize the disclosure of such information to us;
  * We will not knowingly disclose personally identifiable information about you that we collect through the Service to third parties without your consent, except under the limited circumstances described in this Policy; and

We will take reasonable steps to protect the security of the personally identifiable information we collect from you through the Service, including encrypting certain data stored in our database and by hosting our login and registration pages over a secure connection (HTTPS). These Policy highlights are qualified by full reference to the terms described below.

**BY PROVIDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, MEDICAL INFORMATION, OR OTHER INFORMATION TO US OR BY USING OUR SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY AND THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THE POLICY.**

### 1\. INFORMATION YOU GIVE US.

a. _Personally Identifiable Information._ This Policy discusses the Personally Identifiable Information that we collect about you when you use the Service. “Personally Identifiable Information” is information that permits the identification of an individual such as a first and last name; a home or other physical address, including street name and name of city or town; an email address; a telephone number; or a social security number. If information about an individual, including personal health and medical information, is combined with any Personally Identifiable Information, then such additional information is also considered to be Personally Identifiable Information.

b. _The Types of Information Collected._ We collect any information you enter on the Service or give us in any other way (such as through an email, survey, or letter). The information that we collect varies depending upon how you use our Service. Our account registration process requires that you provide us with your user name, birthday and email address, and that you create and provide us with a password. We may also request other information such as your actual first and last name, gender, and zip code. In addition, you will have the opportunity to submit information about your personal medical and health condition to us through, for example, the ovulation calculator, symptom checker, BMI calculator, weight tracking and other tools available on the Site. That information may be associated with your profile and therefore become Personally Identifiable Information. You may access and update your personal information or account settings by logging onto your your profile tab on the Site and changing the information online.

c. _Information in Public Areas of the Site._ Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily provide information in public areas of the Service, such as the user profile pages, question and answer forums, blogs, or user forums, that information can be viewed and possibly used by others. We therefore advise visitors not to disclose personal health information, contact information, including phone number, email address, street address or instant messenger address (within these public areas) that they do not wish to share. We are not responsible for Personally Identifiable Information you choose to submit in these public areas and such information may be freely distributed outside of the Service. Also, we may highlight content you post to the public areas of the Service such as reviews or comments, such as by featuring your Content on the Site’s home page. Information that you post to the public areas of the Site is not considered to be private information.

d. _Minors._ We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, do not attempt to register for our Site or send any information about yourself to us. We recommend that prospective users between the ages of 13 and 17 ask their parents or other legal guardians for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

### 2\. AUTOMATIC INFORMATION COLLECTION.

a. _Cookies._ Like many websites, we use “cookies.” Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. We use persistent, identifying cookies to remember your information and to link your activities to you. While you can take steps to warn off, block or disable cookies, if you do, the Service may not function and appear as we have designed it. Nonetheless, if you want to take these steps, you can do so by following the instructions associated with your browser. Our cookies do not collect Personally Identifiable Information that you provide to us during the registration process, but they do collect other information such as the following:

  * i. the domain name and host from which you access the Internet and the Internet address of the site from which you direct-linked to ours;
  * ii. the date and time you access the Site and pages you visit;
  * iii. your computer’s IP address and information about its operating system, platform and the Web browser type and version you use;
  * iv. demographic and other non-personally identifiable profile information about you; and
  * v. information to combat fraud or misuse.

b. _Pixel Tags._ In our email to you, we use “pixel tags”, commonly referred to as web beacons to determine if your email software or service can display html-formatted email (this helps us optimize the size of our email messages and conserve bandwidth).

c. _Collection of Information by Third Parties._ Our Site may include third-party advertising, links to other websites, and other content from third party businesses. The content posted by these parties will be reasonably identifiable as coming from a third party. We do not provide any Personally Identifiable Information to these advertisers, third-party websites, or other businesses, although on occasion we may mutually share non-personally identifiable (e.g., demographic) information to facilitate delivery of relevant advertisements. These third-party websites, businesses, and advertisers, or advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use tracking technology to deliver (or “serve”) the advertisements that appear on our Site directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize or optimize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other technologies that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party websites or businesses are not covered by this Policy but are covered by their respective privacy policies. Some, but not all, third party advertising companies provide a mechanism to opt-out of their technology.  
We will not provide your private medical information to advertisers, even on an anonymous basis. However, advertisers will be able to track which areas of the Service you visit, make conclusions about your medical condition based on cookies, not account information, and serve advertisements to you that they think will be personally relevant.

d. _Promotions, Sweepstakes, and Contests._ From time to time, we may host a promotion, sweepstake, or contest on the Service. You may be asked to provide personal information or permit the transfer to a third party of your personal information in connection with such promotion, sweepstake or contest. It will be disclosed at the point of collection or transfer who is collecting or transferring the information and whose privacy statement applies, and it will be your choice whether or not you wish to permit such transfer or collection of personal information to a third party.

If you feel that the services could be useful for a third party you know (e.g. your friends or family members etc), you may use our referral service. Keep in mind that this feature is hosted by a third party provider and is subject to the privacy policy of the third party providing the service. If you choose to use this referral service to tell a friend about our site, the third party will ask you for your friend’s email address. The third party will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site.

We utilize an import contacts feature (facebook connect) to help you keep in touch with your contacts [ and/ or other members]. We make it easy for you to invite people from your email address books to join you on our Site. At your request we will search your facebook account to help you import your contacts to our site

We collect third party personal information so that you may send emails to your contacts while logged into the site.

### 3\. USE AND RETENTION OF YOUR INFORMATION.

a. _Use of Personally Identifiable Information._ We use your Personally Identifiable Information, such as your email address for purposes such as responding to your requests, monitoring and providing the Service, maintaining your account, providing you with advertising and non-advertising content that we believe would be of interest to you, enforcing our rights and the rights of third parties, and investigating and ensuring compliance with the Terms.  
We also may use your Personally Identifiable Information to contact you regarding your account.

b. _Opting-Out._ You may modify the types of communications you wish to receive by changing your preferences as part of your profile on the Site. In addition, in our marketing or promotional e-mails to you, we will generally include instructions on how to unsubscribe and/or inform us of your preferences if you do not want to receive any marketing or promotional e-mails from us. You agree that we may send you customary business communications such as acceptance/rejection notices regarding content submissions, general system and administrative messages regarding the Service, address confirmations, and transactional information about your account, and you may not have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such communications so long as you are registered with the Site.

c. _Use of Other Information._ We use non-Personally Identifiable Information about our users for purposes such as measuring the number of visitors to sections of our Site, making the Service more useful to visitors and delivering targeted advertising and non-advertising content. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user’s movement, and gather demographic information for aggregate, non-personally identifiable use.

d. _Retention of Information._ We retain information for as long as required, allowed or we believe it useful, but do not undertake retention obligations. We may dispose of information in our discretion without notice, subject to applicable law that specifically requires the handling or retention of information. You must keep your own, separate back-up records. You may permanently delete and purge your health-related Personally Identifiable Information from the Service; backup copies may exist for a short time in our databases.

### 4\. SHARING OF INFORMATION. We share information with third parties, but only as described in this Section 4 or if authorized by you.

a. _Advertisers and Others._ We share non-personally identifiable information with advertisers, service providers, and other persons with whom we conduct business. Similarly, these advertisers, service providers, and other persons may share with us non-Personally Identifiable Information about you that they have independently gathered or acquired.

b. _Third Party Services._ We contract with affiliated and non-affiliated third parties to provide services to us or to you on our behalf.  
These third parties may have access to your Personally Identifiable Information for use solely in connection with these authorized business activities. We contractually require that our operations and maintenance contractors protect the privacy of your Personally Identifiable Information no less than as required under this Policy.

c. _Business Transfer._ As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or their assets, or engage in acquisitions, mergers, restructurings, changes of control, or similar transactions. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets, and your Personally Identifiable Information may be subject to such a transfer. Also, in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, customer information may be transferred to a bankruptcy trustee or debtor in possession and then to a subsequent purchaser.

d. _Affiliates._ We may share Personally Identifiable Information (excluding personal health information), non-Personally Identifiable Information and other information with our corporate affiliates.  
Corporate affiliates are those entities that we control, are controlled by us, or are under common control with us and any joint venture in which any of the controlled entities may participate from time to time. Any use of your information by our corporate affiliates is subject to this Policy or another policy no less protective of your privacy. Conversely, we may obtain information about you from our corporate affiliates or from your visits to other websites that we or our corporate affiliates control.

e. _Compliance and Safety._ We may release user information when we believe release is appropriate to:

  * i. comply with applicable law, and to respond to legal process, including subpoenas, search warrants and court orders, and to respond to or otherwise address written complaints of copyright infringement;
  * ii. make disclosures under programs intended to prevent potential crimes or investigate persons;
  * iii. enforce or apply agreements, including the Terms; or

### 5\. INFORMATION SECURITY

a. _Your Obligations._ You must protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Please sign off when finished using a shared computer. Your emails to us are not necessarily secure against interception so do not include sensitive information in them. We generally will not ask for passwords in an email and you should assume that if you get such a request, it might be fraudulent. YOU MUST DO WHAT YOU REASONABLY CAN TO ENSURE THE SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.

b. _Our Security Measures._ We take reasonable precautions to protect the security of our user’s information. We have physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to help safeguard, prevent unauthorized access to, maintain data security for, and correctly use your information. These procedures include the use in appropriate circumstances of secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology and computer server firewalls. However, neither people nor security systems are foolproof, including encryption systems. Therefore, while we use reasonable efforts to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### 6\. LINKS.

The Service contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of every web site that collects your personally identifiable information. This Policy applies only to information collected by the Service.

### 7\. CONDITIONS OF USE, NOTICES, AND REVISIONS.

a. _Privacy Concerns._ Your use of the Service and any dispute over privacy is subject to the Terms.

b. _Notice Required by Law._ In those jurisdictions that permit email notice, if we are required to disclose or provide notice of invasion of certain security systems,  
we will do so by email to the most current email address provided by you to us. It is critical that you keep your email contact information correct and updated  
at all times.

c. _Identity Theft._ If you believe that you are a victim of identity theft entitled by law to request information from us,  
write us at our Legal Notice address (see the next section of this Policy) and we will let you know what additional information you must provide to us.  
After we have received that information, we will supply without charge the information legally required to be disclosed that we then have, subject to applicable law and reserving all  
of our rights and defenses.

d. _Revisions._ We reserve the right to change our Policy at any time due to changes in the law, the Service, technology and industry practices.  
Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately.  
If we make non-material changes, we will indicate at the top of this page the revised Policy’s new effective date.  
We encourage you to refer to this Policy at least every 30 days to check for material changes to this Policy.  
It is critical that you keep your email address information correct at all times.
